<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>deserter sleigh (incoming)</VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>deserter sleigh (leaving)</VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>north pole propaganda</VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>A multi-use personal invisibility device engineered based on experimental E.L.F technology for stealthier present delivery. Allows the user to become completely invisible for a brief duration, after which the device requires a short amount of time to recharge.</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>A deserter declassifier is a single-use, ultra-tech device consisting of a brain-scan apparatus and a long, thick needle. It is primarily used by north pole deserters for data extraction. By inserting the needle into the skull of a titled nobility, memories can be downloaded from their brain, forming valuable deserter intel. The amount of intel received is determined by the rank of the noble person. The person affected by a Deserter Declassifier dies in the process, and when used on neutral visitors, it is treated as an act of war.</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>
  <VFED_Intel.description>A dossier containing information about the North Pole. In order to protect the information from the E.L.F counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to obtain contraband items from the Deserters, or to gain access to quests and even assassination missions on North Pole nobility.</VFED_Intel.description>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.description>A dossier containing critical information about the North Pole. In order to protect the information from the E.L.F counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to plan high-profile assassination attempts, but it can also be exchanged into standard intel via the contraband system.</VFED_CriticalIntel.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>Decommissioned North Pole technology since the invention of psylink neuroformers, psychic amplifier upgrades a psylink in the user's mind. It cannot form a psylink by itself, and can only be used by colonists with already present psylink. The user presses the device over the eyes, where it links to the brain directly and restructures part of it. Afterwards, the device disintegrates into a small cloud of snowflakes.</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.description>A small E.L.F crate containing valuables. May contain intel. Opening it requires bypassing several security protocols and takes a short while.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_SupplyCrate.description>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>A small elite E.L.F crate containing extremely valuable items. May contain critical intel. Due to the special restrictions, only titled underlings of Santa Claus are capable of opening it.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>
  
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>auto-sleigh munitions crate</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>A large military crate of auto-sleigh munitions. Will explode when damaged, sending armed shells flying in random directions.</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>

  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>auto-sleigh battery pack</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>A large, overcharged auto-sleigh battery. Will release a strong electromagnetic pulse when damaged, potentially disabling nearby defenses..</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>

  <VFED_Aerodrone.label>auto-sleigh</VFED_Aerodrone.label>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.description>An auto-sleigh is a spacer-tech, unmanned aerial vehicle equipped with advanced sensors and an explosive payload. Designed for autonomous long-range operations, it's commonly used by the E.L.F for reconnaissance and bombardment. Its ability to release powerful explosive salvos makes it effective against various targets. This auto-sleigh is temporarily disabled due to the recharge cycle.</VFED_Aerodrone.description>

  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>E.L.F maxpack</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>The E.L.F maxpack is a formidable armored transport truck, known for its impressive cargo capacity. Its armor is impenetrable, ensuring the safety of its contents throughout transit. Once in motion, the Maxpack’s doors remain sealed until it reaches its predetermined destination. While attempting to loot its cargo is futile due to built-in self-destruct protocols, its robust exterior makes it an ideal shield on the battlefield.</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>

  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>A small surveillance buoy usually deployed around temporary convoy stops. Linked directly with a patrolling auto-sleigh, once triggered, it will call down a small explosive salvo on its location.</VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>
  <VFED_FuelTank.description>A large fuel tank used to refuel North Pole sleighs. Will detonate if damaged beyond a certain point, potentially triggering a chain reaction.</VFED_FuelTank.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>A North Pole computer interface. Linked to the surveillance console, the display bank shows live footage from all surveillance pillars in the sector.</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>

  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>north pole underfarm</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>An underground hydroponics basic used by the North Pole to feed their subjects. Fully automated and connected to water mains, these farms require no labor to operate.</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>

  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>crashed auto-sleigh</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>A crashed auto-sleigh.</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>

  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>E.L.F mega high-shield</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>An advanced shielding apparatus, the Imperial mega high-shield projects a vast momentum repulsor field, allowing shots to exit but preventing any from entering. Specifically calibrated for high angles, it's adept at deflecting incoming mortar rounds, auto-sleigh strikes and even orbital slicer ribbons. The unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield. Draws huge amounts of power.</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>

  <VFED_ZeusCannon.description>An ancient secret of the first elves. it is a closely guarded secret of the North Pole. This formidable artillery piece has the unique ability to convert vast quantities of electricity and christmas spirit into potent energy blasts. With unmatched range, it can pierce the atmosphere to target and obliterate objects in orbit. A testament to lost engineering brilliance, it stands as both a weapon and a symbol of the might of Santa Claus.\n\nIt has a long charging cycle, after which it will aim at the target and release a devastating energy blast.</VFED_ZeusCannon.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>A deserter device capable of intercepting North Pole communication. When activated, it will begin intel scraping, emitting a pulse in regular intervals. Each pulse has a chance of generating a small amount of intel, but it may also increase your visibility and even alert an E.L.F strike force. After 10 pulses, the machine burns out and triggers a fiery explosion.</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Kontarion.description>A powerful, long-range weapon used by the E.L.F to take out enemy targets from afar. Kontarion turret fires ultra-dense uranium slugs at incredible speeds, penetrating even the heaviest armor. With its rapid-fire capabilities, tremendous accuracy and infinite range, it’s a force to be reckoned with. It's more accurate at longer ranges, and can't fire at all close up. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of uranium slug ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Kontarion.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Palintone.description>A powerful, anti-infantry weapon used by the E.L.F to defend unsafe outposts. Palintone turret fires large-caliber shells at incredible speeds, dealing heavy damage over significant ranges. It fires huge volleys of rounds that can provide suppressive fire and quickly shred lightly armored targets. With its devastating firepower, the Palintone turret is capable of keeping even the largest enemy forces at bay. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of autocannon ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Palintone.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Onager.description>A powerful, anti-armored weapon used by the E.L.F to destroy heavily armored targets with ease. Capable of launching missiles in bursts of 6, the Onager can deal devastating damage to enemy forces in a short amount of time. The Onager turret is most effective at short range, where its missiles can be accurately targeted at enemy positions. However, it cannot fire at enemies that are too close, as the missiles require a certain distance to arm and track their targets. Additionally, due to the sheer number of missiles it fires, the Onager is not as accurate as other turrets, and can sometimes miss its targets. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of missile ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Onager.description>

  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>A spacer-tech sleigh designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>

  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>sleigh chunk</VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>A chunk of the sleigh of Santa Claus. It seems to have been torn off by some kind of powerful weapon.\n\nHaving landed not long ago, it still contains useful resources which you can acquire by deconstructing it.</VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>

</LanguageData>
